<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<release_notes>
  <release version="0.1" date="03 March 2011">
    <note type="INFO">Initial Release</note>
    <note type="BLOG">`PropertyGridExtras addin v0.1 – Grow/Shrink font size &lt;http://www.clarionedge.com/clarion/addins/propertygridextras-addin-v0-1-growshrink-font-size.html&gt;`_</note>
  </release>
  <release version="0.2" date="03 March 2011">
    <note type="FIX">There was an issue with restoring the saved font using the incorrect Font.Unit in some circumstances."</note>
  </release>
  <release version="0.3" date="16 Oct 2010">
    <note type="FEATURE">Show Additional Indentation – When set to true, displays Property indentations as the Microsoft PropertyGrid does (except for the first level whose +/- glyphs won’t appear in the left most column).</note>
    <note type="FEATURE">Auto Adjust Label Column – Resizes the label column to adjust itself to the longest label.</note>
    <note type="FEATURE">Themes (using the DrawManger) – There are 3 build in themes and an additional Dark theme that I have borrowed from the SmartPropertyGrid code example.</note>
    <note type="BLOG">`PropertyGridExtras addin v0.3 – now with Additional Settings! &lt;http://www.clarionedge.com/clarion/addins/propertygridextras-addin-v0-3-now-with-additional-settings.html&gt;`_</note>
  </release>
  <release version="0.4" date="21 May 2011">
    <note type="CHANGE">Preparing for public release of source code. Making the VS project work without dependencies, adding docs, etc</note>
  </release>
  <release version="0.5" date="4 October 2011">
    <note type="BLOG">`PropertyPadExtras – Automatic save/restore grid state! &lt;http://www.clarionedge.com/clarion/addins/propertypadextras-automatic-saverestore-grid-state.html&gt;`_</note>
    <note type="FEATURE">Save and restore expanded state of grid categories</note>
    <note type="FEATURE">Expand/Contract all buttons added to the grid toolbar</note>
    <note type="FEATURE">Options button added to the grid toolbar</note>
    <note type="FEATURE">Grow/Shrink font feature now expanded to allow you to also set the font type. Configuration is available in the Options dialog</note>
    <note type="FEATURE">Grid ToolStripRenderMode changed to ManagerRenderMode. This means that the toolstrip will be correctly styled if you have the `SetTheme &lt;http://clarionaddins.com/addins/SetTheme.html&gt;`_ addin installed.</note>
    <note type="CHANGE">Reset font now detects the correct font from the main IDE form</note>
    <note type="CHANGE">Internal code refactored for easier maintenance and better performance</note>
    <note type="CHANGE">Screenshot updated</note>
  </release>
  <release version="0.6" date="8 October 2011">
    <note type="FIX">Create temp directory if it doesn't already exist. Normal this is handled by the IDE but only when you first open a text file for editing, not if you go straight to a property grid!</note>
    <note type="FIX">The property enumerator was not correctly looping over all child properties. This could result in some descendants not being saved/restored.</note>
    <note type="FIX">The initial load of window and report designers is sending a few extra ExpandAll commands. These appear to now be correctly suppressed allowing the restore to function correctly.</note>
  </release>
  <release version="0.7" date="26 February 2012">
    <note type="INFO">Internal Release</note>
  </release>
  <release version="0.8" date="27 February 2012">
    <note type="INFO">Internal Release</note>
  </release>
  <release version="0.9" date="28 February 2012">
    <note type="FIX">Fingers crossed this is the definitive fix for the issues plaguing the restire tree state feature! It looks like I have found the correct way to override the default *expand all* on opening as well as when the grid has focus.</note>
    <note type="FIX">Well... there is **one** catch with the above fix. If you select a control in the designer and move it using the cursor keys then the grid state becomes fully expanded. The good news is that as soon as you move focus away from that selected control the saved state is restored :)</note>
  </release>
  <release version="0.10" date="29 February 2012">
    <note type="FIX">Possible fix for NullReferenceException with C8 build 8973</note>
  </release>
  <release version="0.11" date="7 March 2012">
    <note type="FIX">Possible fix for All state handling issues. Restore state on initial grid loading, on TAB to next property, on moving controls with cursor keys, on multiple selections, etc</note>
    <note type="FEATURE">Option (on by default) to save/restore the property selection. This includes focusing the selected property within the grid!</note>
  </release>
  <release version="0.12" date="7 March 2012">
    <note type="INFO">Internal Beta Release</note>
  </release>
  <release version="0.13" date="7 March 2012">
    <note type="INFO">Internal Beta Release</note>
  </release>
  <release version="0.14" date="8 March 2012">
    <note type="FIX">Remember Selected Property feature now also saves and restores child properties correctly.</note>
    <note type="CHANGE">Toolbar icons are now 24x24 so they look better with default toolbar size</note>
  </release>
</release_notes>